{
    "subject": "resource/The_Magnificent_Ambersons_(film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Film_scores_by_Bernard_Herrmann",
    "human_readable": "The film 'The Magnificent Ambersons' is about Film scores by Bernard Herrmann.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8997403979301453,
            "question": "Who composed the film scores for 'The Magnificent Ambersons'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8840267658233643,
            "question": "What film is 'The Magnificent Ambersons' about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7394227385520935,
            "question": "Could Bernard Herrmann have worked on other films besides 'The Magnificent Ambersons'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7204462289810181,
            "question": "Would a person interested in classical music likely enjoy the film scores by Bernard Herrmann?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.669984757900238,
            "question": "What genre might 'The Magnificent Ambersons' be categorized as based on the film score information?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5899891257286072,
            "question": "Is 'The Magnificent Ambersons' a documentary?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5002680420875549,
            "question": "What type of work did Bernard Herrmann create for films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32779762148857117,
            "question": "Are there famous examples of film scores that have become iconic?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23047330975532532,
            "question": "How might different film scores affect the audience's perception of a movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04962897673249245,
            "question": "What role does music play in enhancing the storytelling of a film?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film 'The Magnificent Ambersons' is about Film scores by Bernard Herrmann.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6437_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might different film scores affect the audience's perception of a movie?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6437_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there famous examples of film scores that have become iconic?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6437_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of work did Bernard Herrmann create for films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6437_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6437_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6437_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6437_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6437_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6437_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6437_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6437_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6437_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6437_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6437_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'} \n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provided contain information about the film \"The Magnificent Ambersons\" and its score composed by Bernard Herrmann, which supports the statement that the film 'The Magnificent Ambersons' is about film scores by Bernard Herrmann."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "While the provided context heavily emphasizes Bernard Herrmann's score for \"The Magnificent Ambersons,\"  it also describes the film as being based on a novel and focusing on a dying American aristocracy.  This suggests the primary subject of the film is not film scores but rather the story itself.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}